jobzilla.ng 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy

**Overview**  
jobzilla.ng (“jobzilla.ng”) knows that you care about  
how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your  
privacy seriously. This policy describes the types of information  
collected, how it may and may not be used, and how it is protected. By  
visiting jobzilla.ng’s website (“Website”), or using any of our  
services on the website (“Website Services”), you acknowledge that you  
accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and  
our use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data  
contained in log files. The information in the log files include your  
IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider,  
such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site  
(such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site  
and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your  
personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only  
showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some  
of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on jobzilla.ng to  
support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as  
cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will  
also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense  
program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser  
you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash  
installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing  
New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or  
showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing  
cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s  
DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are  
browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising  
(including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to  
serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based  
targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous  
browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about  
visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when  
viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses  
“non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal  
information about you, such as your name, email address, physical  
address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account  
numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on  
all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies  
or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing  
preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this  
can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other  
websites. This could include the inability to login to services or  
programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out  
of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow  
cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a  
new cookie will be added.

 **Third Party Sites**  
jobzilla.ng does not control the privacy policies of third party  
sites or service providers to which we provide links. These third party  
sites or service providers may use cookies to provide a service or serve  
ads based on a user’s prior visits to jobzilla.ng. Please be aware  
that if you click on an ad or third party link, you will be subject to  
the third party’s privacy policy.

 **Changes to the jobzilla.ng Privacy Policy**  
You agree that jobzilla.ng may amend this policy from time  
to time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Your  
continued use of any portion of the Website or jobzilla.ng service  
following the posting of the revised policy will constitute your  
acceptance of the changes.

 **Information Collected From Users**  
In the course of your browsing the Website, jobzilla.ng may  
collect the IP address of the computer through which your visit is  
enabled; cookie information; information regarding the pages, links,  
banners, icons and other parts of the Website that are accessed or  
clicked on during a visit to the Website; information regarding the  
date, time, and duration of your visit; and information you may  
volunteer, e.g., in response to survey requests or as part of a  
registration. Upon any registration for, and in subsequent interaction  
with, Website Services, jobzilla.ng may collect mandatory  
information such as your User Name, Password, primary email address,  
etc. A “cookie” is a small line of text that is sent to your browser and  
stored on your computer when you visit a website. jobzilla.ng uses a  
cookie for record-keeping and verification purposes and a cookie helps  
us provide better service to you. For example, we use a cookie to verify  
your session and user identification and to track the pages within the  
Website that you visited. Your browser should have options to accept,  
reject or provide you with a notice when a cookie is sent. However, if  
you disable cookies, you may not be able to use the Website Services.  
Please note that jobzilla.ng does not and cannot read cookies set by  
other websites.

 **Your obligations to other Users**  
As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of  
these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and  
others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of  
like-minded members. Do not abuse the jobzilla.ng service by using  
it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate this Privacy Policy. You  
must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be  
deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, or which may otherwise  
violate the purpose and spirit of jobzilla.ng and its community of  
Users.

 **Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against  
unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or  
destruction of data. However, no data transmission over the Internet can  
be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or  
warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you  
do so at your own risk. We restrict access to personal information to  
employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in  
order to process it on our behalf.

 **Use of Information Collected**  
We use the information we collect to provide our services and features  
to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to  
provide you with customized user experience. We may contact you with  
service-related announcements from time to time. Your information will  
not be shared with any third parties except as explained below.  
As part of our business, we may pass to our service partners  
aggregated information (data gathered up across multiple or all user  
accounts) regarding visitors, users, and historical transactions in a  
manner that will not personally identify any individual user. We may  
aggregate personal information and disclose such information in a  
non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third  
parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these  
situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that  
could be used to identify you personally.  
We will not sell, rent or transfer your Personally Identifiable  
Information to any third party, unless we are required by law, court  
order or regulation, or we believe that disclosure is necessary to  
comply with law or legal process, or to cooperate with local or federal  
authorities, or to protect or defend against fraud, misuse of the  
jobzilla.ng Website, breach of any of your obligations hereunder, or  
to protect our intellectual property rights. In addition, we may  
disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in connection with a  
merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of the assets  
of jobzilla.ng to another company (an “Acquirer Company”), provided  
that such Personally Identifiable Information shall only be used by the  
Acquirer Company in accordance with the terms and conditions of this  
Privacy Policy. jobzilla.ng will not track your Internet usage  
outside of the confines of the jobzilla.ng Website.

 **How to contact us**  
You can contact jobzilla.ng by sending an email to **info[at]jobzilla.ng**
